<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Clear The Stockpiles (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.ClearTheStockpiles</packageId>
  <author>MarvinKosh</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/ClearTheStockpiles</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of MarvinKoshs mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1542424055
with permission.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://dsc.gg/mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/ClearTheStockpiles][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
Adds a new WorkGiver for hauling, which prioritises clearing stockpiles of blockages that may if there are extra products from doing a bill at a work table.

The behaviour of this WorkGiver is as follows:
If an item doesn't belong in a stockpile, first a check is made to see if there is a valid stockpile within a radius of 18 of the item. If so, the item will be taken there.
If no valid stockpile was found or no stockpile with enough space was found, the item will be dumped in a small radius of its original position. This position will not be next to or in a doorway or on top of a trap.

The clearing routine by default runs at a higher priority (85) than hauling corpses (corpses can block stockpiles, no reason not to haul those) but at a lower priority than burying and stripping corpses.

In the mod settings, you can configure the radius in which to search for matching stockpiles, between 1 and 25. There is also a debug mode toggle, please don't use this unless you're troubleshooting the mod.

[Version 1.0.7]

[b]Please ask me before re-uploading this mod.[/b]

[h2]Don't comment asking when the mod will update.[/h2]

I'll post on [url=https://twitter.com/marvinkosh]social media[/url] when there's a mod update. If you have encountered a problem with a mod, let me know immediately - you can @ or DM me on Twtter or on the RimWorld Discord.

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1536294009]Go to the Beta 19 version.[/url]

Go to Ludeon Forums for more information and direct download links: https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=30508.0

If you like this mod, why not consider looking at some of my [url=http://steamcommunity.com/id/marvinkosh/myworkshopfiles/?appid=294100]other mods[/url]?

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] or the standalone [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2873415404]Uploader[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[*] Use [url=https://github.com/RimSort/RimSort/releases/latest]RimSort[/url] to sort your mods
[/list]

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/changelog/2314332319][img]https://img.shields.io/github/v/release/emipa606/ClearTheStockpiles?label=latest%20version&amp;style=plastic&amp;color=9f1111&amp;labelColor=black[/img][/url]</description>
  <modIconPath IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">ModIcon/ClearTheStockpiles</modIconPath>
  <modVersion IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">1.5.0</modVersion>
</ModMetaData>